Midtown Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Addition, 1932-1997, undated, Series 10:; (2.5 linear feet)
  - Oversize Printed Matter, 1973-1977, undated, 10.6:
    - The Kedettes Collection of Brilliant Canvases, undated (Reel 5438, Frame 1184-1194)
Oct. 12-Nov. 24, 1990 Jack Levine: An Overview, 1930-1990 *
Feb. 6-March 7, 1992 The Midtown Flower Show *
Oct. 13-Nov. 14, 1992 Robert Kushner: IV Seasons *
Oct. 13-Nov. 14, 1992 Isabel Bishop: Walking Pictures *
Nov. 18-Dec. 21, 1992 Walt Kuhn: People and Performances *
March 25-April 25, 1993 Bernarda Bryson Shahn: Images and Ideas *
Sept. 9-Oct. 9, 1993 Michael Berget: A Delicate Balance *
Sept. 9-Oct. 9, 1993 Lee Jackson: The Figure in Light and Motion *
Jan. 19-Feb. 26, 1994 Cynthia Knott: Horizons *
Sept. 21-Nov. 5, 1994 Paul Tchelitchev: A Reevaluation *
Nov. 11-Dec. 30, 1994 Paul Cadmus: Still Lifes, Portraits, Tableaux
Jan. 12-Feb. 25, 1995 Jacob Lawrence: An Overview, Paintings from 1936-1994 *
March 2-April 8, 1995 Robert Kushner: Mille Fleurs, a Cornucopia of New Paintings *
Below is a list of exhibitions for which the year or date is unknown.
Date Exhibition
undated Solo Exhibitions, A - Z (by artist)
Jan. 27-Feb. 10 Paintings by M. Azzi Aldrich
Nov. 23-Dec. 9 Paintings by M. Azzi Aldrich
April 17-May 6 Paintings by Saul Berman
Nov. 9-28 Paintings by Julien Binford
March 7-23 Drawings and Etchings by Isabel Bishop
Oct. 3-15 Paintings by Isabel Bishop
Feb. 15-March 4 Paintings by Homer Boss
April 18-30 Paintings and Watercolors by Homer Boss
Oct. 24-Nov. 17 Paintings and Drawings by Paul Cadmus
April 16-29 Feminanities, Paintings by Minna Citron
April 27-May 13 Paintings by Minna Citron
Dec. 14-25 Paintings by Adelaide De Groot
June 8-21 Other Exhibition of Drawings of the Philadelphia Stage Door Canteen and Recent Drawings by Emlen Etting
Oct. 23-Nov. 11 Paintings and Gouaches by Maurice Freedman
Dec. 26-Jan. 12 Paintings of Massachusetts and Pennsylvania by Maurice Freedman
Feb. 1-14 Watercolors by Ethel Katz
Oct. 13-31 Watercolors by Dong Kingman
Oct. 14-Nov. 1 Dong Kingman's Watercolors
undated Watercolors by Dong Kingman
June 6-23 Building the New York World's Fair, Gouaches and Oil Paintings by Renee Lahm
March 23-April 15 New York Murals by Edward Laning
May 22-June 9 Drawings of War in Italy by Edward Laning
Oct. 19-Nov. 4 Sculpture by Oronzio Maldarelli
Oct. 29-Nov. 17 Sculptures in Hammered Metal by Oronzio Maldarelli
March 18-31 Paintings and Watercolors by Joseph Margulies
June 2-21 Drawings by Fletcher Martin
April 20-May 9 Oils, Water Colors, Lithographs, and Drawing by Paul R. Meltsner
April 30-May 18 Oils, Tempera, and Lithographs by Paul R. Meltsner
May 24-June 10 Oil Paintings and Water Colors by Paul Meltsner
May 14-29 Watercolors by Thalia Millett
May 7-27 Watercolors by Kaname Miyamoto
May 1-16 Paintings by Paul Mommer
Oct. 2-18 Paintings by Paul Mommer
Oct. 13-31 Paintings by Paul Mommer
Nov. 1-16 Paintings by Paul Mommer
May 12-31 Paintings by Fred Nagler
Oct. 18-31 Paintings by Fred Nagler
Jan. 4-29 Iowa Landscapes, Paintings and Watercolors by William C. Palmer
March 24-April 12 Recent Wash Drawings by William C. Palmer
Sept. 25-Oct. 14 Paintings and Drawings by William Palmer
Dec. 12 Paintings by William Palmer
Dec. 3-16 Watercolors by Betty Pierson-Parsons
Feb. 15-March 1 Paintings and Sculpture by Alzira Peirce
Oct. 4-17 Paintings by Alzira Peirce
Jan. 7-25 Paintings by Waldo Peirce
March 3-29 Paintings, Watercolors, Prints by Waldo Peirce
Aug. 30-Sept. 25 Six Year Retrospective Exhibition of Paintings by Waldo Peirce
Nov. 16-Dec. 5 Paintings by Waldo Peirce
Nov. 14-Dec. 9 Paintings and Drawings by Siegfried Reinhardt
Dec. 12-30 Watercolors by Lionel S. Reiss
Nov. 2-14 Water Scenes of New York by Saul [Berman]
April 10-25 Watercolors by Eugenie Schein
Nov. 1-19 Paintings by Anatol Shulkin
Sept. 28-Oct. 12 Paintings by Martha Simpson
Jan. 18-Feb. 5 Paintings by Jacob Getler Smith
April 9-27 Drawings and Watercolors by Jacob Getlar Smith
Dec. 27-Jan. 14 Watercolors by Jacob Getlar Smith
Jan. 11-28 Paintings by Miron Sokole
Dec. 10-23 Gouaches by Miron Sokole
March 2-16 Paintings by Isaac Soyer
May 3-21 Paintings by Isaac Soyer
March 2-20 Paintings by Frederic Taubes
Nov. 27-Dec. 22 Recent Paintings by William Thon
undated Paintings and Watercolors by William Thon
Feb. 27-March 10 Watercolors of Mexico by Edward Valentine
March 22-April 9 Sculpture by Arline Wingate
Jan. 14-26 Water Colors by E. Helen Young
Group Exhibitions, date or year unknown
Date Exhibition
undated Group Exhibitions
Feb. 27-March 26 Cooperative Exhibition of Contemporary American Art
May 4-31 Peggy de Salle Presents Little Gallery's 20th Anniversary: Four Nationally Known Artists, Courtesy Midtown Galleries (Isabel Bishop, Stephen Etnier, Zoltan Sepeshy, William Thon)
June 24-July 30 Three Painters from the Midtown, Watercolors, Drawings, Pastels at United Virginia Bank Gallery, Norfolk, Va. (Hans Miller, Jason Schoener, William Thon)
July 31-Aug. 13 Contemporary American Artists Associated with Midtown Galleries of New York, Four Fountains, Southampton